Philip Singer Papers
Philip Singer Papers
- Miscellaneous media
  - Yan Xin Nine Step Qigong, Step One, singer_p_0529; Chinese dubbed into English; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 1)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_0205; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 41)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_0206; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 41)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_0207; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 41)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_0208; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 41)
  - [Untitled], March 14, 1998; singer_p_0209; label reads, "March 14, 1998"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 41)
  - [Untitled], March 14, 1998; singer_p_0210; appears that label fell off tape; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 41)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_0211; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 41)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_0212; note taped to the box reads, "Interviews (or previews, it is not particularly clear): 1. Simon, DVM; 2. Oliver, MD; 3. Potter, D.C.; 4. Lorraine, U.B.D.; 5. Khalsa, MD; 6. Jackson, Pastor; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 41)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_0213; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 41)
  - [untitled], singer_p_0224; label offers a few words ("pts," "Steve," "ads"), but no indication of title and content; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 42)
  - [untitled], singer_p_0426; MiniDV; running time 30:00 (Box 46)
  - [untitled], singer_p_0427; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 46)
  - [untitled], singer_p_0428; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 46)
  - [untitled], singer_p_0429; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 46)
  - [untitled], singer_p_0430; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 46)
  - [untitled], singer_p_0431; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 46)
  - [Untitled], 01/05/1998; singer_p_0485; VHS: VHS-C; running time 30:00 (Box 48)
  - [Untitled], 1979/04/02; singer_p_0826; cassette has one word written on it, but it is illegible; Audio cassette; running time 30:00 (Box 49)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_0834; handwritten text on tape has been crossed out; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Box 50)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1353; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 53)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1422; small label on case reads, "Disc 6, side 1 JF [illegible] xx cont'd - 44:00"; CD; running time 44:00 (Box 55)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1423; small label on case reads, "Disc 1, side 2 chorus - Mexico 51:00 [bad quality]"; CD; running time 51:00 (Box 55)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1424; writing on disc reads, "Disc 4, side 2 channel 3-2," and on the case it reads, "K. reading in church?"; CD; running time 44:00 (Box 55)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1425; writing on disc reads, "Disc 1, side 1 Mexico"; CD; running time 58:00 (Box 55)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1437; writing on disc reads, "#7 side 1, track 1 xxxx 44:00"; CD; running time 44:00 (Box 55)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1438; writing on case reads, "JK"; CD; running time 60:00 (Box 55)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1450; CD; running time 30:00 (Box 55)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1570; Flash Memory: USB (Box 43)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1571; Flash Memory: USB (Box 43)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1572; Flash Memory: USB (Box 43)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1573; Flash Memory: USB (Box 43)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_0830; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Box 50)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1420; CD; running time 60:00 (Box 55)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1421; small label on case reads, "Disc 4, side 2 - end whistling mid-ghost"; CD; running time 60:00 (Box 55)
  - [Untitled], singer_p_1511; Hi8; running time 20:00 (Box 58)
  - [Untitled] #2, singer_p_1558; Mini-cassette; running time 60:00 (Box 43)